<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  ~     PowerSwitch by Max Rosin & Markus Ressel
  ~     Copyright (C) 2015  Markus Ressel
  ~
  ~     This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
  ~     it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
  ~     the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
  ~     (at your option) any later version.
  ~
  ~     This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
  ~     but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
  ~     MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
  ~     GNU General Public License for more details.
  ~
  ~     You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
  ~     along with this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
  -->

<resources>

    <string name="tutorial__got_it">OKAY</string>

    <string name="tutorial__room_explanation">
        This tab displays all your receivers grouped by rooms. This is
        the new Control Central for your home :)
    </string>
    <string name="tutorial__scene_explanation">This tab shows all your scenes. Using scenes you can save
        configurations of receivers for easy access at later time. An example would be a scene called \"Garden lights\"
        which turns on the pond lighting, the path lighting and the rear house lighting. Another example is the
        \"Cinema\" scene which turns on the TV and amplifier but also turns off the ceiling light.</string>
    <string name="tutorial__timer_explanation">This tab shows all your timers. With timers you can let PowerSwitch
        automatically perform actions for a given time and day of the week. An action can be anything from
        switching a single receiver or switching a hole room to activating a scene. An example could be
        the coffee machine, that turns on every morning at 6:00 am during the work week.</string>
    <string name="tutorial__sleep_as_android_explanation">In this tab you can configure actions for the alarm clock
        app \"Sleep As Android\" Wie bei Timern können Aktionen auch hier sowohl einzelne
        Steckdosen, ganze Räume oder auch Szenen sein. Mögliche Events sind das aktivieren des Alarms, das
        Snoozen (wenn man noch ein bisschen im Bett bleiben möchte) oder wenn man den klingelden Wecker
        abschaltet. Ein Beispiel wäre die Nachttischbeleuchtung, die beim Klingeln des Weckers an geht, beim
        Szoozen wieder aus geht und beim deaktivieren des Weckers wird zusätzlich zum Nachttischlicht noch die
        Kaffeemaschine eingeschaltet.</string>


    <string name="tutorial__add_new_roms_and_devices_here">Add new Rooms and Receivers using the + button</string>
    <string name="tutorial__first_add_room">At first create a room to add your devices to</string>

</resources>