<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  ~     PowerSwitch by Max Rosin & Markus Ressel
  ~     Copyright (C) 2015  Markus Ressel
  ~
  ~     This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
  ~     it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
  ~     the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
  ~     (at your option) any later version.
  ~
  ~     This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
  ~     but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
  ~     MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
  ~     GNU General Public License for more details.
  ~
  ~     You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
  ~     along with this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
  -->

<resources>

    <string name="tutorial__got_it">OKAY</string>

    <string name="tutorial__room_explanation">
        This tab displays all your receivers grouped by rooms.\n
        \nThe new Control Center for your home :)
    </string>
    <string name="tutorial__scene_explanation">This tab shows all your scenes.\n
        \nUsing scenes you can save configurations of receivers for easy access at later time.\n
        \nAn example would be a scene called \"Garden lights\" which turns on the pond lighting, the path lighting and
        the rear house lighting. Another example is the \"Cinema\" scene which turns on the TV and amplifier but also
        turns off the ceiling light.
    </string>
    <string name="tutorial__timer_explanation">This tab shows all your timers.\n
        \nWith timers you can let PowerSwitch
        automatically perform actions for a given time and day of the week. An action can be anything from
        switching a single receiver or switching a hole room to activating a scene.\n
        \nAn example could be the coffee machine, that turns on every morning at 6:00 am during the work week.
    </string>
    <string name="tutorial__sleep_as_android_explanation">In this tab you can configure actions for the alarm clock
        app \"Sleep As Android\".\n
        \nJust like with timers you can add receiver, room and scene actions. Possible events are the ringing alarm,
        snoozing and disabling an active alarm.\n
        \nAn example would be turning on your bedside lamp when an alarm goes off, turning the light off again when
        you snooze the alarm and when you finally disable the alarm to stand up the light goes on again and the
        coffee machine starts to work.
    </string>
    <string name="tutorial__apartment_explanation">
        In this tab you add and configure apartments.\n
        \nDifferent apartments have different rooms and scenes. You can assign Gateways to each
        apartmens, so network signals are only sent to gateways in the correct apartment.\n
        \nSelect an apartment by tapping it, modify it by press&amp;hold.
    </string>
    <string name="tutorial__backup_explanation">
        Create and restore backups of PowerSwitch in this tab.\n
        \nBackups contain the complete app state, including rooms, scenes, timers, settings etc.
    </string>
    <string name="tutorial__gateways_explanation">
        In this tab you can add and configure Gateways.\n
        \nGateways are the connection between PowerSwitch (your smartphone) and your power plugs.
        If you want to be able to control your power plugs on the go simply enter a DynDNS address
        instead of an IP. After proper router configuration you are good to go :)\n
        \nAdd a Gateway by pressing the plus button, modify them with press&amp;hold.
    </string>
    <string name="tutorial__wearable_settings_explanation">
        In this tab you can manage any setting of the wearable companion app.\n
        \nChange vibration feedback, highlight the last used button, choose a different theme&#8230;\n
        \nNote: To properly sync settings with your watch, please open the wearable companion app
        on your watch while changing settings. Then close and reopen the wearable app and the changes should apply.
    </string>

    <string name="tutorial__geofences_apartment_explanation">
        In this tab you can add and configure geofences for specific apartments.\n
        \nGeofences allow you to make actions based on your location. Actions can be specified for enter and exit
        events. Geofences in this tab are always connected with an apartment, so the location of the geofence is
        also used for other features of PowerSwitch (like auto switching between apartments).\n
        \nExample: Turn off all your lights when leaving your apartment and turn them on when you come home
        again.
    </string>
    <string name="tutorial__geofences_custom_explanation">
        In this tab you can add and configure geofences.\n
        \nGeofences allow you to make actions based on your location. Actions can be specified for enter and exit
        events.\n
        \nExample: Turn off all your lights when leaving your apartment and turn them on when you come home
        again.
    </string>

    <string name="tutorial__add_new_roms_and_devices_here">Add new Rooms and Receivers using the + button</string>

    <string name="tutorial__first_add_room">At first create a room to add your devices to</string>

</resources>